{
    "subject": "resource/Jean-Paul_Sartre",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Alexandre_Koj\u00e8ve",
    "human_readable": "Jean-Paul Sartre was influenced by Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9830219745635986,
            "question": "Did Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve have an impact on Jean-Paul Sartre's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9771400094032288,
            "question": "Can you name any works by Jean-Paul Sartre that reflect the influence of Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9688628315925598,
            "question": "Who influenced Jean-Paul Sartre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9325432777404785,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Jean-Paul Sartre and Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9247919917106628,
            "question": "Who were some of the prominent thinkers that influenced Jean-Paul Sartre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9179493188858032,
            "question": "What were some key concepts or theories shared by Jean-Paul Sartre and Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8854773044586182,
            "question": "How did Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve's thinking differ from Jean-Paul Sartre's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8228065371513367,
            "question": "What were the main areas of study or expertise for both Jean-Paul Sartre and Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7894574999809265,
            "question": "In what historical period did both Jean-Paul Sartre and Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve live and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41992461681365967,
            "question": "What philosophical ideas did Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve explore?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jean-Paul Sartre was influenced by Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7385_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what historical period did both Jean-Paul Sartre and Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve live and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7385_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the main areas of study or expertise for both Jean-Paul Sartre and Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7385_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve's thinking differ from Jean-Paul Sartre's?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7385_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7385_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Jean-Paul Sartre was influenced by Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve. The document mentions that \"Perhaps the most decisive influence on Sartre's philosophical development was his weekly attendance at Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve's seminars, which continued for a number of years.\" This suggests that Sartre was indeed influenced by Koj\u00e8ve."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents support the statement that Jean-Paul Sartre was influenced by Alexandre Koj\u00e8ve. Specifically, multiple documents mention Sartre's attendance at Koj\u00e8ve's seminars as a significant influence on his philosophical development."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}